## **Contacts**

- © Edinburgh, UK
- +447831417609
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/dmytro-ruzhytskyi
- https://github.com/dmitruz

My Portfolio

## **Tech Skills**

HTML

CSS

**JavaScript** 

React

Vue.js

**TypeScript** 

Node.js

MongoDB

FireBase

SQL

**JQuery** 

PHP

SASS

Bootstrap

## **Soft Skills**

Flexibility and adaptability

Leadership skills

Personal qualities

Teamwork

Punctuality

Sociability

Attention to details

## Languages

English: Fluent Ukrainian: Native

# **Dmytro Ruzhytskyi**

#### **Full-Stack Web Developer**

I am motivated and development oriented person with experience in Frontend and Backend development. I am keen on writing clean and mutable code for building my applications. My experience ranges from pure HTML, CSS, JavaScript development to React framework and basic Node.js development. I get on well with people at all levels, can easily make good working relationships.

## **Projects**

- Restaurant menu app [Vue.js] https://restaurant-dishes.netlify.app/
- **2.** Window Glazing [HTML, CSS, JS, Gulp, Mamp] https://windows-glazing.netlify.app
- **3.** Weather forecast [HTML, JS, CSS, API] https://dmitruz.github.io/Weather\_forecast
- **4.** Lose weight app [HTML, CSS, React, Node.js] https://weightloss-webhive.netlify.app
- **5.** Gym App [HTML, Vite, React TypeScript, Bootstrap] https://evogym-group.netlify.app

## **Work Experience**

#### Front-End Web Developer UpWork

October 2022 - up to now | Edinburgh, Scotland

Duties: Created web pages, applications, landing pages, updated content. Developing user-facing web applications and reusable components.

#### Front-End Web Developer Binnerals

September 2021 - October 2022 | c. Sofia, Bulgary

Duties: Adaptive and cross-browser markup of web sites and applications.

Optimization of codes. maintained of web products. Developing user-facing web applications and reusable components.

### Sales Manager TsemBud Resurs

July 2010 - April 2019 | Khmelnytskyi, Ukraine

Duties: Achieved growth and hit sales targets by succesfully managing sales team. Build and promote strong, long-lasting customer relationships by partnering with them and understanding their needs

## **Education**

#### **GOIT**

#### **Fullstack Developer**

May 2021 - April 2022 | Online

#### National University of Environmental and Life Science of Ukraine

#### Forestry engineer

September 2004 - April 2010 | Kyiv